playster.com 2019-02-01

# Playster - Privacy Policy

_Effective as of May 25, 2018_

Playster is committed to protecting the privacy of our users and members. The Site and the Application are, offered to you by Playster Corporation (“Playster”, “we”, “our” or “us”).

To provide you with the best possible service, Playster needs to collect some information about you. In the following paragraphs, this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) will describe and explain our policy and procedure regarding the collection, processing, treatment, use and disclosure of your information, including certain information that may identify you (“Personal Data”), when you use our [www.Playster.com](https://www.playster.com/) (the “Site”), sign-in as a user, use our services, features, content or applications, including the Playster mobile application (the “Application”), or interact with us in other ways (collectively, with the Site and the Application, the “Services”).

### What does this Policy cover?

This Policy explains how we may collect, store, use or otherwise process your information, including your Personal Data. We respect your privacy and will take reasonable steps to protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. In addition to this Privacy Policy, we may choose to notify you of other privacy policies which could apply upon the collection or sharing of your personal data.

More specifically, this Policy will explain:

  * the type of information we may collect about you;
  * how we use the information we collect;
  * when we may use the information you provide to contact you;
  * the circumstances under which we may disclose your details to a third party; and
  * the rights you may have regarding your information.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you may gain access to through the Services or to individuals that we do not manage or employ.

When you click on a third party logo displayed on or in the Services, and it links you to a different website or application, you are acknowledging that our Privacy Policy no longer applies to that website or application. You must read the privacy policies of the Third Party Services to see how your personal information will be handled on such Third Party Services.

While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. Accordingly, we encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

### What information do we collect?

To enable us to personalize, improve and continue to operate our Site and Service, we may receive and store the following information about you:

Direct Identifying Information/ Profile Data: This includes your name, address, email address, username and password, as well as any additional information you provide us with when registering for our services.

Indirect Identifying Information: We automatically receive and record certain information from your device or web browser when you interact with our sites, e.g. your internet protocol (IP) address, mobile device ID, time zone setting, location data, language preference, operating system and platform. We may also create a user ID that may be used similarly to identify you indirectly.

Payment Information: In order for you to register for our and Services or make purchases on our Site, we will need to collect your credit card details.

Location Data: To assist with our analytics and to provide you with a more tailored service, we may collect data which tells us where you are. We may also collect the language option or country you choose. We may link location data to other information we have collected about you.

Marketing and Communications Data: This may include information about your subscriptions to newsletters and your marketing preferences.

All data collected will be securely and safely stored on servers specific for this purpose.

### How is the information collected?

We may collect information from you in the following ways:

Information You Provide Us: This information includes data you provide on registration such as your name, e-mail address, date of birth, gender, credit card information, billing address, SIP code and/or postcode and other information (“Personal Information”). We may also collect information if you participate in a survey, promotion, competition or sweepstakes, if you contact us through our customer support team or if you adjust the preferences in Your Account.

Information We Collect Automatically: This is the information collected when you use our Services. This may include, but is not limited to, information about the device you used to access our Services, your IP address, browser and software features, referral URLs, crash reports and your activities and use of our Service e.g. which movies you watch and what books you read.

Information Collected Through Cookies: For more information about Cookies, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.playster.com/legal/cookie).

### How is the information used?

The information you provide us with is essential for us to provide the Service. For example we use your Personal Information to:

  * monitor, develop and improve the Services and/or your experience based on a monitoring of your preferences and behaviours;
  * administer the provision of your Services;
  * process payments and/or collections;
  * process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by or about you;
  * investigate any suspected breach of or Terms and Conditions or the breach of other terms and conditions otherwise relating to you;
  * investigate any suspected fraud occurring on your account; and
  * contact you if you are the lucky winner of a sweepstakes or competition.

### The Collection, Use and Handling of Children’s Information

In accordance with our Terms and Conditions, only individuals 18 years and over may use our Site and Services. If you are aware or become aware of any person under the age of 18 using our Services, please contact us immediately and, unless permission is obtained from their parent and/or guardian and/or the bill payer, we will take steps to delete their account and all Personal Information.

We are committed to protecting children’s privacy on the Internet and we comply fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). In accordance with COPPA, we will never knowingly solicit or accept Personal Information from users known to be under eighteen years of age. If you are under the age of thirteen, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any personal information about yourself.

If we learn that we have received any Personal Information from a user under eighteen years of age, we will take appropriate steps to remove that user’s Personal Information from our records. Moreover, if a parent becomes aware that a child has provided us with personal information, we ask that the parent or legal guardian of the child contact us by visiting www.playster.com, selecting ’Contact Us’ and use the appropriate contact information or contact us at [privacy@Playster.com](mailto:privacy@playster.com).

### Marketing Messages

Typically, we will only send you marketing emails if you consent to us doing so. You can unsubscribe from this part of our Service at any time. If you do subscribe to our marketing email service, we may periodically contact you to tell you about any additional services, special offers and upcoming promotions or events offered by us, our subsidiaries, our affiliates or our marketing partners that we think may be of interest to you.

### Who is the information shared with?

We will never sell your information. That being said, we may share your information in the following ways:

Your Public Postings: If you post a review or make a comment anywhere on our Site, Service or platform and your post contains your Personal Information, those details may be shared with other Users to have access to that particular part of our Service.

Sharing with Third Party Providers: We use third party service providers to be able to offer the best possible Services to you. At times, we may need to employ external vendors, service providers and suppliers to assist us with e.g. processing credit card payments, fraud scoring and prevention, debt collection and telecommunications. These third parties may need access to your Personal Information as is reasonably necessary to perform their obligations and are not permitted to use your Personal Information for any other reason.

Sharing with Affiliate Companies: Subject to your approval, we, our affiliates and subsidiaries (where we have granted the appropriate permissions) may disclose certain Personal Information and other details relating to the use of our Service to their respective affiliates and business partners so as to send you their own Direct Marketing communications. Should you wish to revoke your consent to the aforementioned disclosure of your Personal Information and other details relating to the use of our Services, you may opt-out by either (a) checking the appropriate “Opt Out” box in any applicable email communication or electronic newsletter, or (b) emailing the Privacy Team at [privacy@Playster.com](mailto:privacy@playster.com)

Third Party Features: We may, at times, include on our Sites additional features and functionality from third parties. Some of these features may require us to send selected information about your use of our Service (e.g. content viewed) to third parties. If you do not wish for Us to share this information, you may opt out. We will never send your password or your financial information to any third party through these features or functions.

At times, we may include additional features and/or functionalities from third parties on our Site or Service. Certain of these features may require that we communicate select information about your use of our Service (such as, for example, Content consumed) to said third parties. If you do not wish for us to share this information, you have the option of opting-out by sending an email to the Privacy Team at [privacy@Playster.com](mailto:privacy@playster.com) Note that the information communicated in this manner will never include your passwords nor your financial/payment information.

Cleaned Data: Playster will periodically remove, hash, scramble, anonymize, aggregate or summarize certain elements of Personal Information relating to its users. In doing so, the resulting information (the “Cleaned Data”) would no longer be considered personal information and, as such, would no longer be subject to this Policy. The Cleaned Data may be transmitted to various third parties as necessary so that we can provide you with our Services.

Business Restructuring: In the event of a reorganization or restructuring, we may be required to share elements of your Personal Information within our group of companies so as to be able to continue to deliver our Services to you without interruption. This may also be the case if we were to participate in a merger, acquisition, reorganization, restructuring or other event in which some or all of our assets are sold or change ownership.

Please note, however, that if, due to a merger, acquisition, reorganization, restructuring or other event, there is a change in ownership, your information, including but not limited to your Personal Information may be subject to the new owner’s policies. In such circumstances, you will be notified by e-mail or through an update of this Policy prior to the change.

Legal Necessity: Where permitted or required by any law or regulation we may collect, use or disclose your Personal Information or other information without your consent, e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena or to comply with a legally permitted inquiry by a government agency.

We may also share your information to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues.

Be assured that, whilst we may share your information as indicated above, your Personal Information and other information will remain subject to and will be governed by this Policy at all times.

### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We take the protection of your Personal Information seriously and we endeavour to take all reasonable measures to protect any information we collect, use, store or disclose. Where possible we have implemented technological and organisational procedures designed to protect the integrity and security, and to ensure the appropriate use, of your Personal Information. These procedures are proportionate to the nature, sensitivity and format of the personal information collected, used, stored or disclosed by us.

Our users in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and European Union (“EU”) should be aware that some companies we work with to provide our Services operate outside the EEA. We only let that happen if we are satisfied with their levels of security. So, keep in mind that when you give us Personal Information it could be transferred, stored or processed in a location outside the EEA or EU.

### Transfer of Data

We maintain servers in various locations worldwide and therefore your information may be processed in a jurisdiction different from the one in which you live. We comply with data protection laws in all applicable jurisdictions and provide equal protections to all information.

### Retention of Your Information

Any Personal Information given to us will only be held for as long as legally required or permitted and in accordance with the following measures. We will only retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary for us to provide you with our Services or have a legitimate reason to keep it.

### YOUR RIGHTS IN RELATION TO YOUR INFORMATION

Depending on where you live, e.g. if you reside in the European Union and/or the European Economic Area, you may have certain legal rights relative to the collection and use of your Personal Information. You may have the right to:

  * (a) Change and update your information as necessary;
  * (b) Have the entirety or part of your Personal Information to be erased or “forgotten”;
  * (c) Delete your Personal Information at any time and for any reason;
  * (d) Object to, restrict or limit the use of your Personal Information; and
  * (e) Ask us for a copy of your Personal Information.

You can do all of this by contacting our Privacy Team / Data Protection Officer at [privacy@Playster.com](mailto:privacy@playster.com)

Where the law provides, you may also send queries to your local data protection authority.

### Changes to This Privacy Notice

This Policy was last updated on May 25, 2018. We reserve the right to make changes to this Policy at our discretion. Note that this page will be updated to reflect any changes to this Policy and therefore, we recommend that you review this page periodically.

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please visit [www.Playster.com](https://www.playster.com/) select ’Contact Us’ and use the appropriate contact information or contact us at [privacy@Playster.com](mailto:privacy@playster.com)

### Data Protection Officer

If you have any questions pertaining to the collection, use and storage of your Personal Information or any questions relative to this Privacy Policy contact our Privacy Team at [privacy@Playster.com](mailto:privacy@playster.com).

### Data Controller

The data controller of your Personal Information is Playster with Registered office at 2000 rue Peel, Suite 420, Montreal, Quebec, Canada H3A 2W5. Please be aware that if you contact us to assist you, we may need to authenticate your identity before fulfilling your request.
